Live, love and give as good as you get.
Fish Tank is a drama film directed by Andrea Arnold.
Fifteen-year-old Mia is in a constant state of war with
her family and the world around her.
When she meets her party-girl mother’s charming new boyfriend Connor, she is amazed to find he
returns her attention, and believes he might help her start to make sense of her life.
Mia Williams, played by Katie Jarvis.
Connor O'Reily, played by Michael Fassbender.
Joanne Williams, played by Kierston Wareing.
Tyler Williams, played by Rebecca Griffiths.
Billy, played by Harry Treadaway.
Billy's Brother, played by Jason Maza.
Fish Tank is a 2009 British coming of age drama film
written and directed by Andrea Arnold.
The film is about Mia, a volatile and socially isolated 15-year-old,
and her relationship with her mother's new boyfriend.
Fish Tank was critically acclaimed and won the Jury
Prize at the 2009 Cannes Film Festival.
It also won the 2010 BAFTA for Best British Film.
It was ranked 65th on the BBC's 100 Greatest Films of the 21st Century list.
It was also ranked 91st on The New York Times' list of
the 100 Best Movies of the 21st Century.
The film was funded by BBC Films and the UK Film Council.
It was theatrically released in the United Kingdom
on 11 September 2009 by Curzon Film.
The film explores themes of adultery, friendship, mother, alcohol, fight.
The tone is emotional.